All right, perfect.
Well,
I know it's your your birthday tomorrow,
right? So, I guess
happy birthday and and how does this
feel for you a day early? Yeah, man, it
feels awesome. It feels like a blessing.
You know,
thank God, you know, my birthday and the
draft always aligns up every year, so
it's a good early birthday gift.
Awesome. How much contact did you have
with the Saints over the course of the
off-season? And you know, is this a
place that you expected to be a
possibility for with? Yeah.
Um
Not Not a Oh, can you guys still see me?
Uh there you go. We got you now. Um
yeah, not too much communication
throughout the process.
I'm pretty sure we met like at the
Senior Bowl.
Don't remember sitting down at the
combine too much, but
yeah, not too many communication.
And I I wouldn't say I really expected
to get picked up by the Saints.
With the I know every team is going to
be different, but when you talk to
teams, what was their vision for you and
and where you fit best in the NFL? Yeah,
a couple different teams had different
visions. Some have corner with nickel,
some have safety with nickel, some have
safety.
So, a couple different teams have
different visions of what they see.
Where do you feel like you fit best?
I feel like I can fit anywhere. I feel
like I can play all five positions in
the backfield.
So, if I need to line up at corner,
nickel, or safety, I feel like I can be
ready to go at either one.
TJ, how did that Senior Bowl experience
go for you to help you put you in this
position?
Yeah. No,
it really helped me a lot, especially I
got a chance to play nickel a lot while
I was at the Senior Bowl. So, getting
that experience at like a NFL level was
really awesome and helped me prepare for
this day where I'm at today.
During your time over at Iowa, it seemed
like every year you kind of got better
and more comfortable. What was kind of
that that that final year like for you
and what do you feel like you you
achieved there? Yeah. Man, it really
just was putting in the work every day.
Had full confidence in the work I put in
and the ability I had. So, just going
into the season, you know, just wanted
to
really accomplish being a complete
corner, you know, being in the run game,
while also defending each team's best
receiver and making as many plays as I
can on the ball.
Now, going in the seventh round, like
just to see your name called, what did
that mean to you? Just
Yeah. Yeah,
it meant a lot. No matter what round it
was, I knew it was going to like hit me
deep because this is a sport I've been
playing all my life. So, just even hear
hearing my name called today was a
blessing.
Everything that was kind of written
about you throughout the pre-draft
process talks about your physicality.
Would you say that that's a a big part
like a hallmark to your game or or is
there another thing that you emphasize?
Yeah, I would definitely say that's a a
big part. You know, I feel like I'm a
competitor, so I I bring that
physicality not only in the run game,
but also
with receivers, you know, pressing at
the line, getting hands on. So, just
being a physical player overall.
And are you Have you gotten a Did you
get any chance to talk with like Saints
defensive staff, like guys like Brandon
Staley or anybody like that? No, sir.
Not yet. Are you aware of kind of what
the the system looks like? Just going
back to like even Fangio comparisons and
things like that. Not too much. Maybe
just slightly a little bit, but not too
much. So, definitely want to get
familiar more with it.
So, TJ, what's your
day been like then just sitting away for
that call? Yeah, really just sitting
around with family, friends, having some
food,
just watching the draft, you know, just
patiently waiting for my name to be
called.
You played other positions beyond
corner, right? Like
coming Like coming up, I mean. Yeah.
Yeah, played quarterback, receiver,
safety, corner,
about almost everything.
Kind of a dumb question, but just
interested in your perspective. The
experience playing quarterback and
receiver, just how does that help you
now as a corner? Yeah, it helps me a lot
understanding what quarterbacks and
receivers like to do, what they like to
show. So, I feel like I use that for my
game on the
defensive side, you know, just picking
up cues and stuff that, you know,
somebody that might not play both ways
might not get all the time.